Every time he came to see me,
he wore a suit and...
What's wrong?
Somebody!
Take him to the hospital!
Hurry!
Doctor!
How is Benefactor Li?
He was severely poisoned.
We couldn't save him.
He has passed away.
What?
Severely poisoned?
What kind of poison was it?
We don't know
the exact poison yet.
I still need to run tests on the toxin.
It'll be six hours
before the toxicology report is ready.
Thank you for your help, Doctor.
I remember Benefactor Li once said
he always had a Mastermind backing him,
helping him evade the Chunmei siblings' assassination.
So who do you think this Mastermind could be?
But how did this Mastermind
manage to find out about
the Chunmei siblings' plan?
Kid,
you wait here for the report.
Your master and I
will go back to investigate Benefactor Li's cause of death.
I'd rather stay here
than go clean up that dump of yours.
Let's go.
Benefactor Li's meals were prepared in the cafeteria.
His water was from the communal boiler room.
Everyone at the station eats and drinks the same things.
No one else was affected.
Since neither the food nor the water was poisoned,
how was he poisoned?
Looks like
we'll have to wait for the hospital's toxicology report.
A reanimated corpse!
Master Li has become a reanimated corpse!
Do you think that Mastermind
is also from Li Mansion?
Right now, clues about this Mastermind
are just too scarce.
At the moment,
we can't make an accurate judgment.
Master!
Kid! Kid!
Where's the toxicology report?
It's not out yet.
I saw...
I saw Benefactor Li's reanimated corpse!
Xun,
are you spinning a tale?
You can't just make things up.
I...
He was completely dead.
The hospital confirmed it.
What reanimated corpse?
If I'm lying,
may lightning strike me!
I saw it with my own eyes.
He walked right out of the morgue!
Fine, fine. Let's go to the hospital.
Wait.
Go to Li Mansion.
To Li Mansion?
Wait!
We were a step too late.
There's a strong smell of gasoline.
This charred corpse...
...is indeed Benefactor Li.
Enlarged knuckles.
The height matches.
But how could a corpse...
...get here all by itself?
Chief.
So, did Benefactor Li...
...die an unnatural death,
...or a natural one?
This man died twice.
What should I put as the cause of death in the file?
Jiang Huai,
what do you think?
He didn't set himself on fire.
Someone burned the corpse.
They did it to destroy the evidence.
Damn it.
We fell for a diversionary tactic.
Hurry back to the hospital!
The toxicology report might have been stolen.
Wait for me!
Young man.
Just wait a moment.
The report is almost ready.